[Music]
the world is changing and investors
around the world are becoming more
sophisticated demanding innovative
solutions from wealth and asset managers
combining our deep expertise and
experience in both investment and wealth
management manulife investment
management offers fully integrated
solutions spanning investment funds and
pensions globally
strategically positioned in key markets
our investment and client service
operations are supported by seasoned
investment professionals across the
globe
today we are one of the leading global
wealth and asset managers
what sets us apart is our three
complementary global business lines to
meet the unique needs of our clients
with our multi-product and multi-channel
offerings our retail investments arm
brings institutional capabilities to
retail investors creating unparalleled
investment solutions
while our institutional asset management
arm provides a comprehensive suite of
outcome-oriented solutions to
institutions internationally
our retirement arm offers an open
architecture platform which aims at
providing best-in-class products and
end-to-end solutions to meet the varied
retirement needs
leveraging the strength of our parent
company manulife financial corporation
which has a rich heritage and investment
track record that dates back to the
1800s
we have access to a wealth of experience
with our strong insurance pedigree we
manage risks in a strategic and dynamic
way
[Music]
in asia our unrivaled presence and deep
understanding of the region enable us to
offer strong local insights and
flexibility in customizing solutions for
every client
it is our unwavering commitment in asia
that makes us a trusted partner of many
across the world
leveraging our local level expertise as
well as extensive global resources and
network we deliver solid investment
results not just in public markets
but also private markets
our long track record and deep
capabilities in private assets means you
can tap into a diverse group of assets
to meet your unique investment needs
[Music]
through our differentiated value-added
public and private asset offerings and
capabilities we punch above our weight
and delivering outcome-oriented and
goal-based investment solutions to our
clients
and this sums up our commitment to you
manulife investment management